BOKOTO!
Cutter!
Nice one, nice one, Cole, hey!
Get him, get him, Cole, hey!
Okay, one more!
Huh?
Really? That was fast.
Hey, I think we have a chance to pull this off!
I guess that BOKOTO guy's really nothing to be scared of.
It's not like he's gotten blocked yet today.
And he doesn't seem to be particularly off his game.
What is causing this?
Hey, what's going on with you today?
Try to cheer up, my man.
I just wanted to play in the main arena too!
BOKOTO's weakness number six.
His thirst for the spotlight.
I mean that arena!
It's so much bigger and there's so many more people watching that game!
It's total bullcrap!
BOKOTO!
We'll be right back.
Whoa.
Crap.
I didn't notice them at all.
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
I think I was way more nervous than I realized.
Oh, Daichi, now that I see you up close, you're like huge!
What?
Like fat?
No, I mean like an all-around big dude.
Hello, Kurokawa!
I guess he's one of the old players.
Oh!
Our mentor's mentor!
Hidata!
Tadashi!
Kageyama!
Tsukishima!
You guys come here too!
Now then, this is Tashiro.
He was captain when I was a first year, and that's Kurokawa, who was captain when I was a second year.
Hello!
Hey!
Oh man, those two are supposed to be first years?
Unfortunately, yes.
They should have some lunches for us.
So go talk to Kyoko and make sure everybody gets one.
Yes, sir!
So that first year setter and the short middle blocker, what's their deal?
Kageyama?
Well, he's our setter.
He's amazing.
He's in the running for the all-Japan youth team.
And the little guy there?
Uh, what's the best way to describe him?
Hyper little punk.
A tiny freak of nature.
How was he in middle school?
He was completely unknown.
But sometimes that kid, he's an inexplicable force of nature.
That's his deal.
He picked a fight with Ushiwaka from Shira Torizawa.
Seriously? THE Ushiwaka?
An inexplicable force.
Huh?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure the other schools here, they think the same about all of you now.
Go, win your next match.
Yes, sir!
I wanted to do that.
I wanted to tell them to win.
Sorry.
Oh, man.
He's good.
But I mean, look.
Pretty much every team that made it here is going to have some amazing players.
Nice receive, dude!
Nice one!
Oh!
Alright!
Yeah!
I can't take much more.
It's exhausting.
Um, I think you might be taking this on just a little too much, Asahi.
You both have some satisfying receives going on.
No!
Way out!
There was nowhere else you could go with that.
One touch!
Fukunaga!
Yeah!
Hah!
Whoa!
Yeah!
That's right.
Hey!
We're going to have some time after we eat,
so you guys can do a little shopping if you want.
I'm going to go buy a way of the ace shirt!
Wait, Hinata, I'll go with you!
That's Karasuno's setter.
Seems like he can see absolutely everything.
He's definitely got a presence.
Maybe it's time for me to go check out the new t-shirts, too.
I'm thinking about buying a new t-shirt to wear at practice.
That one ain't small!
Please?
I just wanted to play in the main arena, too!
The main arena is so much bigger!
Not fair!
We were careless.
At last year's Nationals, we didn't play until the eighth match.
And the games before ours went long, so we didn't start until after 7 p.m.
There were hardly any spectators or players in the stadium.
And the worst part of the whole damn game was keeping this guy motivated.
It's so cold.
But we're playing in the middle of the day this time.
We thought everything would be totally fine.
It didn't bother you!
I mean, you knew the whole day yesterday this is where we'd be playing?
You really think I'm going to accept that you can't play just because I'm like...
Yeah, he'll get into it eventually.
This happens all the time.
We'll just deal with it.
Bokuto's almost never on point anyway.
I'm glad I can count on my mentors, at least.
Tell us more!
Bokuto sure switches into emo mode fast.
That dude is dead serious about his stuff.
But on the other hand, I don't think he'll ever truly understand.
Having a hard time playing because of nerves?
I'm choking.
I don't ever have trouble handling any pressure coming from outside.
Don't worry.
It'll be fine.
Oh.
Because we are definitely the stronger team.
Fukurodane Academy is slowly catching up.
But to be honest with you, I would have expected to see just a few more spikes from their ace, Kataro, Bokuto.
Bokuto was the player that Eewa High School was most worried about, so they may be a bit confused as to how this is playing out.
Konaha!
Got it!
Looks like a dump!
Star!
Nice kill!
Yeah!
Oh, hell yeah!
Okay, he's starting to get restless.
It's almost time.
Bokuto.
Hmm.
This is basically the actual center court.
Oh.
Yes.
The main arena is bigger, and it has more people.
But at best, only about a quarter of those people would actually be watching you.
Here, while we're in this arena, we're the only ones competing.
Which means everyone here is watching you.
Yeah, but the number of people watching is pretty much the same.
Just one more push.
Besides,
your pupil is here to see you.
Hey!
He saw us!
Bokuto!
Be honest, I still don't really understand what makes Bokuto tick.
Something that would be ridiculous to most people can be very important to him.
Bokuto up!
Look, look!
You've got three blockers!
Hey!
Whoa! There it is!
That's what I was looking for, Phil!
We're playing volleyball now!
Whoa!
He put that shot right on the line!
It's because we're in the sub-arena
that the crowd is closer,
and he can hear exactly what they're saying.
Notice me, Bogato!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
We're lucky the little guy from Karasuno
showed up at just the right time.
It's a good thing you spotted him.
Yeah, but either way,
if Hinata hadn't come over to this court
to watch us play,
I'd have gotten him pumped over something else.
You know, Akashi,
there are lots of times you can ignore Bogato,
and it's fine,
but there are other times when we really do need
to get him back to playing his game.
And one way I contribute
is bringing out part of Bogato's potential.
Besides that,
it's really satisfying to watch him play
when he's on the court doing his absolute best.
So why don't you tell him that to his face?
No, don't do it!
His head will swell until it explodes!
Yes!
You were right!
The secondary arena's the best!
Fukurodani is so good!
Right?
Hey!
Can I get that one in a small?
Hm?
Huh?
What the hell just seems to be
in the tower?
What the hell exactly?
I said to him I'm desires to play
while I'm obsessing.
Why is he like Jessie andвон?
No, I'm sorry.
You have a ticket.
Please accept to be apes contreknove.
You have fabricatheerใช buy narratives.
Why?
Deal?
I know more money.
I'm a surpreite man ever.
I proposed exemptions.
I had to function,
especially after a largeoo …
I would've checked.
Hope will get one person.
Uh, what's wrong?
Do you know him, Hinata?
I don't.
No, I don't know him.
I have no idea who he is.
But if I look away, he wins!
Oh, Hoshiyumi.
Good to see you.
Oh, hey, Kakeyama.
What's up?
Did you guys play yet?
My team won earlier.
Well, that's cool.
Congratulations.
Thanks for that.
So then I guess you two know each other?
We trained at the Youth Intensive together.
This is Hoshiyumi.
Intensive?
So these two are on your team.
Yeah.
Tell me, what position do they have you playing?
I'm a middle blocker.
How tall are you?
A hundred sixty-five centimeters.
He gave himself an extra centimeter.
What's the highest reach you've ever gotten?
Three hundred thirty-three centimeters high.
I win.
What are you still doing down here, Karai?
Game before ours is almost done.
Oh well.
See you later.
Yeah.
When Coach yells at you, leave me out of it.
Whatever.
I didn't want the grit shirt to sell out.
Uh, yeah, dude.
I'm pretty sure there's not much demand for that one.
You don't know!
Um, everybody knows.
Welcome back.
Where's Coach Yukai?
He got caught by some friends of his grandfather's, and he's still stuck talking to them.
How are the matches going?
One guy down there is awesome.
Kamo Medai's number five.
Oh, here he is.
Karai Hoshiyumi.
169 centimeters.
Left!
Oh, he actually hit over that block.
That guy is a really good player, isn't he?
Has he ever, like, been in a magazine?
Not yet.
Apparently he absolutely hates doing interviews.
Really?
I think I'd be super excited to do an interview, even if it was just for the school paper.
Hmm?
Where are you going now?
To watch from up close.
Karai!
Stuffed like a pan-fried pork dumpling!
Could you see that block?
He is on fire!
The kid is looking real good.
Again?
Wow!
That kid can do anything.
Who is that number five?
We have ourselves a service-ace!
Hot dog!
Hoshiyumi does it again!
He's a force to be reckoned with!
This pint-sized one-man army is on a roll, Joe!
He is indeed, he is truly, the Tiny Giant Incarnate!
Oh, wow.
You know, guys, Hinata's gone up against a two-meter Titan without batting an eye.
But now here's someone with his same height disadvantage, and he's already reaching his full potential.
That might be a pretty big shock to his psyche.
Just a random thought.
Hoshiyumi, wait up!
You are amazing out there.
Congratulations on your win.
Oh, thank you very much.
The team's average height was 180 centimeters, which means that essentially every one of their players was quite a bit taller than you.
What was that like?
That's not good.
Huh?
He hates questions like, how can you play when you're so small?
Or what's it like to be short?
Or is the game too tall?
For as long as I've known him, whenever he pulls off a badass play, people tell him, you're such an amazing player for someone so small.
And he tells them, I'm an amazing player, period.
Compared to the rest of the world, 180 centimeters is actually on the shorter side, right?
Uh, the world?
Are you only interviewing me because I'm a short person?
Oh, well, um...
But the main thing that Karai hates most in the whole world is to be told that the reason he lost is because he's so short.
Everyone is too obsessed with this idea that being short means you should give up on everything.
Look, my height is what it is.
It may be a bit of a disadvantage in a volleyball game, but it does not make me helpless!
Okay, okay, I'm sorry about that.
He can be a bit, well, difficult at times.
Now I'm difficult?
All she was trying to do was give you a compliment.
You said yourself that your height puts you at a disadvantage.
Like it or not, it's still amazing that you're helping the team win despite that disadvantage.
You're too self-conscious, man.
Well, maybe you need to learn how to sugarcoat things sometimes!
Sure.
Now go on.
I apologize to the nice lady.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
That's okay.
Oh, Hinata's back.
Come on!
Coach Yukai's back, so we're taking off soon.
Huh?
I am...
I'm so happy I made it here.
I guess I got myself all worried over nothing, huh?
Attention every damn one of you.
I'm learning from you, too.
You all need to start freaking out a little more.
Well, now.
Hmm?
Look, guys, it's the trailer park tit, Willows.
Good job, kids.
You made it all this way.
Be ashamed if you had to turn around and go home.
Yeah, well, it really wasn't that far.
Alright.
You hicks just try to survive again tomorrow.
Oh, don't worry.
We will.
Look at that.
Both of them stopped smiling the second they turned around.
Surviving day two.
I was suddenly reminded as we walked back to the hotel
of just how difficult it was going to be.
But first, as is it for me...
Music
Pressure, that's what I was asking
I don't need the help of God
Egoist, what's that?
I don't have a reason to win
I can't be able to win
I've been able to win
We are! 怯えることない
We are! 隠しやかわれ
高く 高く 高く 舞い上がれ
足割った 敗北の傷は
涙やって 花を咲かせる
諦めろと 笑えばいいさ
そんな言葉 僕は知らない
深など 笑えばいいさ
Niama Girls High School
So they're at that hotel next door
The disparity
And those girls are already in, right?
I mean, they won the girls enter high, so
I guess they were just off somewhere practicing
They're like queens
I bet all their meals
are all-you-can-eat buffets
That reminds me
I love how crispy they fry up all the salmon here
Nothing beats the unlimited rice refills
Yeah, and I could eat omelets until I start laying eggs
Hey, Friyoon
I heard Karasuno won their match today
Congratulations
Uh, thanks
So I...
Well, um...
Good luck...
Tomorrow
I...
Yeah
Okay, see you later
Great
You've definitely got a chance there
Oh, damn it!
I was pretending not to know
And I mean, honestly, it's way more than just a chance
I thought so at the opening ceremonies
I'm pretty sure she likes you
Stop it, please!
I...
have a...
chance
Next time
Day 2
Have a great day
I will hit you
How about this B